Guide to the Duke Forest Records, 1931-ongoing UA.10.09.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0036, 1
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L13-24 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L25-36 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L37-48 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L49-58 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L59-67 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L68-80 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L81-93 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L94-106 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L107-119 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L120-132 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L133-145 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L146-158 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L159-171 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L172-184 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L185-197 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L198-210 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L211-223 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L224-237 (does not include 235) (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L238-250 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L251-263 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L264-276 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L277-289 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L290-302 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L303-311 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L312-324 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L325-337 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L338-353 (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L354-359 (Box 15)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G2-19 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G46-70 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G71-83 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G85-99 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G100-166 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G167-818 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G182-191 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G192-204 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G205-218 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G221-238 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G241-261 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G263-299 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G306-316 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound with Yellow Tape: Longleaf Pine G317-329 Field Records (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in Twine: Shortleaf 75 Plots (Box 16)
  - Graphs: Difference in Gradient Position (2 copies) (Box 16)
  - Graphs: Mixed Pine Hardwoods (7 copies) (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Coile-Schu: Loblolly Pine: Understory Vegetation General (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine (CP+G): Discriminant Functions to Test Effect of Drainage on Presence of (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Certain Understory Species Graphs (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetation Red Gum (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Hawthorne (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Black Gum (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory White Oak (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Southern Red Oak (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Red Maple (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Yellow Popular (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Myrtle (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Water Oak (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Dogwood (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Holly (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Red Sumac (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Vegetations Elm (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Post Oak (Box 16)
  - Files Bound in String: Loblolly Pine: CP+G: Understory Pursimmon (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: Gulf (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: A3-A69, A90-A95 Not Thinned Slash Pine Plantations Office Records (Gulf) 24 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: 2001-2022 Not Thinned Slash Texas Office Records (Gulf) 25 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: 2025-2059 Not Thinned Slash Texas Office Records (Gulf) 26 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: L13-L31 Not Thinned Slash LA Office Records (Gulf) 27 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: T1-T14 Not Thinned Slash Texasa Office Records 28 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: Folder 1 (Continued) (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: Ala. & Miss Gulf Plot No A7-M89 Slash Thinned Office Records 29 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: Texas & LA Gulf Plot No 2002-L29 Slash Thinned Office Records 30 (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: South East: Coastal Plains (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: Coastal Plains (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Coastal Plain Loblolly Not Thinned Office Records 1 (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Coastal Plain Loblolly Thinned Office Records 2 (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: Piedmont (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Piedmont Loblolly Not Thinned Plot No NC1-NC234 Office Records 3 (Box 16)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Piedmont Loblolly Plot No SC2-SC174 Not Thinned Office Records 4 (Box 16)
  - Folder 3: GA Piedmont Loblolly Plot No G2-G21 Not Thinned Office Records 5 (Box 16)
  - Folder 3: NC & SC Piedmont Loblolly Plot No NC39-NC166 Thinned Office Records 6 (Box 16)
  - Folder 3: NC & SC Piedmont Loblolly Plot No NC167-SC78 Thinned Office Records 7 (Box 16)
  - Folder 3: NC & SC Piedmont Loblolly Plot No SC79-SC202 Thinned Office Records 8 (Box 16)
  - Folder 3: GA Piedmont Loblolly Plot No G3-G23 Thinned Office Records 9 (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: Sand Hills (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: NC & SC Sand Hill Loblolly Plot No NC141-SC159 Not Thinned Office Records 10 (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: NC & SC Sand Hill Loblolly Plot No NC14-/SC156 Thinned Office Records 11 (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: Gulf (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: A2-A74, L208-L31, M51-M83, T11,2031-2051 Gulf Loblolly Not Thinned Office Records12 (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: A1-A72 Gulf Loblolly Plot No A1-A72 Thinned Office Records 13 (Box 16)
  - Folder 4: L2-L32, M61-M88, 2023 (1 of 2), 2040 Gulf Loblolly Thinned Office Records 14 (Box 16)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine Plantations Office Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: Coastal Plains (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: NC & SC Coastal Plains Slash Not Thinned NC8-SC66 Office Records 15 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: NC & SC Coastal Plain Thinned Slash Plot No NC1-NC190 SC15-SC112 Office Records 16 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: GA Coastal Plain Slash Plot No GA26 & GA 27 Thinned Office Records 17 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: Piedmont (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: NC & SC Piedmont Slash Not Thinned Plot No NC211, SC101-SC153 Office Records 18 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: GA Piedmont Slash Not Thinned Plot No G9-G15 Office Records 19 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: NC & SC Piedmont Slash Thinned Plot No NC23 SC 203 Office Records 20 (Box 17)
  - Folder 1: GA Piedmont Slash Thinned Plot No G1-G25 Office Records 21 (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Sand Hills (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Sand Hill Slash Not Thinned Plot No NC134 SC158 Office Records 22 (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: NC & SC Sand Hill Slash Thinned Plot No NC135 SC 150 Office Records 23 (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Folder with No Description with spreadsheets (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations Plot 4-28 Field Records S.E. Coastal Plain (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash pine Plantations Plots 29-40-55 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Field Records Plot No M49-A95 Lob F Slash Pine Plantation Gulf (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 209-234 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 235-256 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 181-208 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 156-180 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 131-155 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: Field Records Plot No 2001-2059 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations Gulf (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: Field Records Plot No L1-L32, T1-T14 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations Gulf (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: Field Records Plot No G1-G27 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: Field Records Plot No A1-A48 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations Gulf (Box 17)
  - Folder 3: SECD Loblolly Pine Field Records 1, 2, 3, 41, 43, 189, 190, 203, 231, 244, 246 (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 56-80 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 86-105 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 106-130 Field Records (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Field Records Plot No NC1-NC50 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Field Records Plot No NC51-NC100 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 4: Field Records Plot No NC101-NC150 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No NC 151-NC200 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No NC 201-NC234 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No SC1-SC50 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No SC51-SC100 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No SC101-SC150 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Field Records Plot No SC 151-SC246 Loblolly Slash Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Folder 5: Loblolly Pine Plantations (Box 17)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. VIII 6/99 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. VII 1/1/98 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. VI 1/1/97-12/31/97 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. II 1/93-4/2/95 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. I 4/91-12/92 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. XIII 11/1/97 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. XII 4/1/97-10/31/97 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. XI 10/24/96-3/31/97 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. X 2/12/96-10/23/96 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. IX 4/7/95-2/11/96 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. VIII 2/23/95-4/6/95 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. VII 9/26/94-11/30/94 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. VI 1/1/94-7/14/94 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. V 6/23/92-12/31/93 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. IV 02/01/92-6/22/92 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. III 09/01/91-01/31/92 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. II 08/91 (Box 18)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Correspondence Vol. I 1987-07/31/91 (Box 18)
  - Urban Land Institute Vol. V (Box 19)
  - Urban Land Institute Vol. IV (Box 19)
  - Urban Land Institute Vol. III (Box 19)
  - Urban Land Institute Vol. II (Box 19)
  - Urban Land Institute Vol. I (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill, Isotria medeoloides Blackwood Division (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Blackwood Division Research (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Testimonial Letters (Box 19)
  - OC Landfill Case Study: Spring '93 ENV 101/EGR 115/PP5 149 (Box 19)
  - Landfill Background Literature (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Seal (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Census Data (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill: Assorted Maps (Box 19)
  - OC-17 Geophex site investigation Spring 1995 (Box 19)
  - Property: OC-17 Pickett/Sprouse Appraisal (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC17 Miscellaneous Copies (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. V 01/01/97-12/31/97 (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. IV 01/01/96-12/31/96 (Box 19)
  - Planning: OC Landfill Newspaper Clippings Vol. III 4/5/95-12/31/95 (Box 19)
  - FACTS I file (Box 20)
  - FACTS I RING DATA Tree and Soil Data (Box 20)
  - RESEARCH: Henedrey/Strain C02 Tree and Soils Data (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I GRID DATA Plot Data Sheets (Box 20)
  - FACE Ring 7 & 8 Sector Measurements (Box 20)
  - FACTS -1 Trailer/Building Info. (Box 20)
  - RESEARCH: Hendrey/Strain C02 Project Vol. I: Correspondence, initial site set up material (Box 20)
  - RESEARCH: Hendrey/Strain C02 Project Vol. II: Correspondence, initial site set up material (Box 20)
  - INVOICES: Hendrey/Strain Project Vol. 1: Blackwood Division 1992: Invoices (Box 20)
  - STRAIN/Hendrey Invoices Vol. II Summer 94- (Box 20)
  - FACE project, Blackwood Division: Invoices (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Vol. 1a.: Schlesinger (12/22/94-10/25/95): Correspondence and site set up materials (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I: Site work & Invoices Vol.1b (fall 1995-2/5/96): Invoices and backup (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Vol. 2: Schlesinger (10/25/95-1/30/96): Site set up documents, Orange County permits (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Vol. 3: Schlesinger (01/30/96-present): Site set up documents (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Site Work & Invoices Vol. II (2/5/96-3/31/96): Invoices and backup (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Site Work & Invoices Vol.III (4-1-96-5-31-96): Invoices and backup (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Site Work & Invoices Vol. IV (6/1/96-8/30/96): Invoices and backup (Box 20)
  - BLACKWOOD-FACTS-I, BROOKHAVEN: Project Expenses (Vol. V, Sept. 1996-June 2000) (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Procedures and Protocols for Cooperative Investigators (Box 20)
  - FACTS/FACE Construction-Operations Costs: Summaries and correspondence (Box 20)
  - FACTS-I Lab/Office Trailer: Leasing info and early billing (Box 20)
  - New Hope Corridor Committee: Background Info (Box 21)
  - Inventory 2000 Background Info (Box 22)
  - Haw River Property Info (Box 23)
  - 35 mm slides/various topics (Box 24)
  - History/Archaeology (Box 25)
  - Background for Duke Forest Book (Box 25)
  - OC Landfill (Box 2)
  - OC Landfill (Box 27)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: DU (Box 28)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: DU & DA (Box 28)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: KO (Box 28)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: KO & BL (Box 28)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: BL (Box 28)
  - 2000 Forest Wide Inventory: HI & EN (Box 28)
  - 1991 Inventory: DU (Box 29)
  - 1991 Inventory: KO (Box 29)
  - 1981 Stand Inventory: KO (3) (Box 29)
  - 1985 Stand Classifications: vol 1&2 (Box 29)
  - 1979 Inventory: Preliminary (Box 30)
  - 1979 Inventory: (1: 3) (Box 30)
  - 1975 Stand Classifications: vol 1&2 (Box 30)
  - 1997 Duke Forest Cover Type Mapping (Box 31)
  - 1986 Cover Type Mapping Field Sheets: Duke Homestead & Durham Division (Box 31)
  - 1986 Cover Type Mapping Field Sheets: KO, BL, EN, HI, DA, Dodsons (Box 31)
  - 1990 Inventory Data (Box 31)
  - Duke Forest Records "Brain Book" Copy (Box 31)
  - Wildlife Survey: Fall 1996: "Duke Forest Neighbor Survey" (Box 31)
  - 1975 Cover Type Notes: BL (Box 32)
  - 1975 Cover Type Notes: DU (Box 32)
  - 1975 Cover Type Notes: KO (Box 32)
  - DF Master's Projects Dec 91-Mar 93 Vol 5 (Box 32)
  - DF Master's Projects Apr 93-Dec 95 Vol 6 (Box 33)
  - DF Master's Projects Jan 96-Dec 00 Vol 7 (Box 33)
  - DF Master's Projects Jan 01: Vol 8 (Box 33)
  - DF Master's Project 1982-1985: Vol 3 (Box 34)
  - DF Master's Project 1985-1990: Vol 4 (Box 34)
  - Extra Copies of old LOGs (Miscellaneous years) (Box 34)
  - DF Master's Project 1963-1978 Vol 1 (Box 35)
  - DF Master's Project 1978-1981 Vol 2 (Box 35)
  - Soil Surveys (DU, OR, AL Counties) (Box 35)
  - Certification Forest Stewardship Council, 2001-2010 (Box 36)
  - Certification Sustainable Forestry Initiative, 2001-2004 (Box 36)
  - Certification Sustainable Forestry Initiative Miscellaneous (Box 37)
  - Certification Southern Center for Sustainable Forestry (Box 37)
  - Certification General Information (Box 37)
  - Harvesting, 1964-1986 (Box 38)
  - Old Stand Records Durham C1-10 (Box 38)
  - Old Stand Records Durham C13-27 (Box 39)
  - Old Stand Records Durham C28-55 (Box 40)
  - Old Stand Records Durham C56-80 (Box 41)
  - Old Stand Records NHC/KO C1-23 (Box 42)
  - Old Stand Records NHC/KO C24-32 (Box 43)
  - Old Stand Records Hillsboro C1-8 (Box 43)
  - Old Stand Records: Miscellaneous (Box 43)
  - Stand Data: Korstian 1981 C1-40 (Box 44)
  - Inventory 1941 (Box 44)
  - Inventory Old and Miscellaneous (Box 44)
  - Inventory Old and Miscellaneous (Box 45)
  - Stand Records: All Divisions, circa 1980s, 1990s (Box 46)
  - Plantations Records: All Divisions (Box 47)
  - Inventory 1952 and Miscellaneous (Box 48)
  - Oosting Natural Area Miscellaneous (Box 48)
  - Duke Forest Literature Card Catalog 1974 (Box 48)
  - Unknown box of 4x6" notation sheets (Box 48)
  - Annual Reports 1999-2003 (Box 49)
  - Budget Prep 1999-2007 (Box 49)
  - Duke Forest Research Board Vols. 1&2 (Box 50)
  - Management: Burns 1979-2000 (Box 50)
  - Seedling Counts 1983-2000 (Box 50)
  - Site Prep 1982-2000, Non-bid sales 1981-2005, Bid sales 1999-2003 (Box 50)
  - Management: Bid sales 1987-1998 (Box 51)
  - Ed/Out: Tours and Activities 1980-2003 (Box 51)
  - Western Field Trip Photos (Box 51)
  - Judd's Daily Log Books (Box 52)
- Accession UA2018.0073, 2
  - Research Projects: Forest Wide: Carbon Off-sides Project (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Eno, 4 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Hillsbourough, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Haw River, 4 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Korstian, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Oosting, 5 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: NCFS Fred White Project C20 Korstian (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Seth Reice New Hope Creek Proposal (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Hardwood Research Program C24 (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Sea-Level Research Project (Box 53)
  - Research Projects: Teaching and Research Completed Report Forms and Questionnaires, 1998-2007; 10 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Barnes-Experimental, 7 folders (Box 53)
  - Research Projects (General Research): P-Z, 18 folders (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Permanent Sample Plot Report, 1952-1963; 6 folders (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Permanent Sample Plots, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Permanent Sample Plots Remeasurement, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Permanent Sample Plots Proposals (Peete, Christensen), 1978-1988 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Christensen/Peete Citations, Reprints, Papers and Proposals, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Research Support and Development (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Publications List (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Webpage Faculty Citations, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Webpage Old and New Citations, 1999 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (General Research): Bibliography Duke Forest Research, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Research Locations Durham General (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): SunShares: J Rivin Compost Project (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Oren, Ram Cypress Plantation (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Ecotox Farm Ponds (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): PSP Study Durham Division (Peete and Christensen), 11 folders (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Rausher, Mark Durham Division Field Prepartion (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Sign Construction Acid Deposition Project (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Statler, Richard Shortleaf Billings' Plots, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Virginia Tech Southern Pine Beetle Chemical Supression (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): C-70, Global Change Research Site (Coop Agreements), 8 folders (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): RO System (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): OT Septic Tank (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Phase I (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Site Development Plans (Box 54)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): OT Phones (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): OT Power (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): OT Soil Survey (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): OT Site Well (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Commercial Forest Research Program (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Sigmon/Maury Global Climate Change Research Site, 3 folders (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Richardson, Kurt Field Genotype Study (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Michael Acra Research Area Preparation (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Drainage Project, Durham C-70 (Boyd Strain and Richard Thomas) (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Durham C-70 Strain/Thomas Site Modifications (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Stand History, Durcham C-70 Research Site (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Southern Commercial Forest Project --Invoices/Billing (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Strain/Boyd, Research C-70 Durham Division (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Strain Site Invoices, 1994-1996 (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Durham Division): Strain, Boyd Air Quality Research Site Invoices/Billing, 1992-1993; 1994-1995 (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Blackwood Research Locations, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS 1 Publicity (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS Brookhaven Electrical Services for Wireless Transmitter (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Oren, ACES/Stem Flow Boxes (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS Site Equipment Enclosures/ ACES Oren (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Finzi/Drake Trenching FACE (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACE Site Tower Electrical Upgrades (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Blackwood Field Project Expenses (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS ! Other FACTS Researcher Invoices, 3 folders (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I Fertilization Experiment (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Duke Forest FACE Experiment Continuation to DOE, 2001 (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I Continuation, 1998 (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Proposed Research for FACTS, 1995 (Box 55)